1st day after transplant
head is 1 little swollen
but not so much
it's on man
Oh she comes here
but it's normal because I took a lot of anesthesia
I'm washing my hair here now or pass the spray
have to wait for about ten minutes
is on
man i'm so round
see,
you're not even giving it to put a banner
my sky god
good news
as you can see
look at my face bro
how it sank
some parts are still swollen
is on
but much less
my ear has already glued Igor back
see a face
I don't know 1
2 days I believe I go back to normal like this
so happy old man
day 5
Or can you see how it's already deflated enough Cara
1 marquinha stayed here
here too
my bend is normal
already returned here
already returned
the ear has already closed more
how nice no bro
that collapsed that tavaço already speak the real
day six
look at how the face is
alone
very little here in
part of the eye
are you seeing
this is day seven
the swelling of the eye has come out
look there
scratching here on the side
but it's good
I just arrived in São Paulo
oh I didn't see the time to go back to Brazil from now on
so i'm going to play more in the stories this stop there
of hair transplantation
progression to progress,
right?
how much this is evolving or not
otherwise it will stay
every day
day eight
day ten
day twenty
closed people
I just got to the ember let's go marching
that's it bora left